{
    "id": "392f9bd9f277490493674f32010fe5ea",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He died ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1572aa2865f847b7b394d2f68944bc41"
        },
        {
            "question": "We usually go and see Granny ……………………… Sundays.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e8b42f209ca41e49be5b9281943c4c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will meet again ……………………… a month’s time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cad443f872f34a62ae47995cd820609a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you see the helicopter ……………………… the palace?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "above"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dca16b1b69f04b88aa7acf1fc573f150"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to be ……………………… 18 to see that film.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "above"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b06ce0ad401547bd8964bd5086a28b7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked right ……………………… the desert.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "through",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a83897a930bc46f2960aa0231c6153f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Summit of Everest is about 8000 meters ……………………… sea level.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "above"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c7d716e99a0641e9be1ab2fba2e0963d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw the child running ……………………… the road.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "on",
                "along"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e86f9692e2424c03bb258f0cf101bf86"
        },
        {
            "question": "Stop standing ……………………… and do some work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "about",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c04b80aa57384af49b8d310cea3bc4aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Bowness is ……………………… Lake Windermere.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "above",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "604d9b24977341bd8ffd05802d7fcfb5"
        }
    ]
}